show about the window everything's wet
yo guys we rented an airstrip
[Laughter]
this is so cool this is so cool so
there's two runways I don't know which
ones longer we get two runways oh my god
they're really right thousand cones
let's go it does it come VC money spent
wisely
oh oh shit I got a chicane cries
whoa and this is all ours oh man this is
great
what is this
[Music]
[Laughter]
whose uncle
brand-new five years of tires do I
scratch it up
no this entire box what do you think
that one's doing out here
yeah it's a condo in the Prius are two
cones
[Laughter]
yo this place is incredible this is so
much fun it's great
alright scope is uh I think we're gonna
have fun without you guys but um yeah me
seize your money is well-spent how many
we get
[Music]